elegantmarketplace.com 2016-02-03

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement reviews how Elegant Marketplace collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.elegantmarketplace.com. It also outlines the options available to you with regards to our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**Personal Information**

As is the standard policy of most Web sites, Elegant Marketplace automatically gathers information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to:

  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Potentially conduct research and analysis
  * Potentially display content based upon your interests

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving communications from us including our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in these emails or you can contact us at [info@elegantmarketplace.com](mailto:info@elegantmarketplace.com).

**Information Sharing**

We do not sell your personal information to third parties.  We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If Elegant Marketplace is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * To any other third party with your prior consent.

**_PayPal_**

If you choose to use PayPal as the payment gateway to complete and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

As is the standard policy of most Web sites we may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

_Web beacons_

Web beacons allow us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.  Pages on this website contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used in conjunction with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use the Elegant Marketplace website. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Elegant Marketplace includes links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Elegant Marketplace. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. It i s our suggestion that you carefully read the privacy statement of any web site you visit.

**Security**

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and after we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on Elegant Marketplace, you can contact us at [info@elegantmarkeplace.com](mailto:info@elegantmarkeplace.com).

In order to complete your oder and make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for that order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at info@elegantmarkeplace.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Additional Policy Information**

Our Web site includes widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company. Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [info@elegantmarketplace.com](mailto:info@elegantmarketplace.com).

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at [info@elegantmarketplace.com](mailto:info@elegantmarketplace.com)
